(Sheldon:)...whose work has brought him
to the precipice...
(Sheldon:)...of forever changing mankind's
understanding of the universe, a.k.a. me.
(Sheldon:)And here, we have a waitress
brushing her teeth with her finger.
(Sheldon:)A.k.a. you.
(Leonard:)Sorry.
Is this supposed to be buttering me up?
(Sheldon:)Please hold all questions
until the end of the presentation.
(Sheldon:)This is the Large Hadron Collider
at CERN in Switzerland.
(Sheldon:)The product of decades
of planning and construction.
(Sheldon:)It is a mecca
for physicists the world over.
(Sheldon:)This is Bath and Body Works
on Colorado Boulevard.
(Sheldon:)They sell scented soaps and lotions.
Some of which contain glitter.
(Sheldon:)Now, let's see
if we can match the individual...
(Sheldon:)...to the appropriate destination.
(Penny:)Okay. Show's over.
(Sheldon:)No, it's not. I've got five more slides.
(Penny:)Sheldon, this is Leonard's decision.
(Penny:)He invited me to Switzerland
and I intend to go.